A Finding Aid to the George Tooker Papers, circa 1851-2010, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, circa 1900-2010; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; 1.1 Linear feet Boxes 4-5, 8
  - Photographs by PaJaMa, Rome and Venice, Italy, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Photographs by PaJaMa, Various Locations, circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15-18)
  - Photographs of Artists by George Platt Lynes, circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
  - Photographs of Artists by George Platt Lynes, circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Artists by George Platt Lynes, circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13-16)
  - Photographs of Bureau by George Tooker, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Photographs of George Tooker and Others, circa 1930-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18-20)
  - Photographs of George Tooker and Paul Cadmus, 1947-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Photographs of George Tooker and Installation View, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Photographs of George Tooker, circa 1950-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - George Tooker and William Christopher with Dog, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - George Tooker Passport Photographs, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - William Christopher Passport Photographs, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Photographs of William Christopher, circa 1949-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Phillips Academy Class of 1938 Reunion Photograph, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Group Portrait, Young George Tooker at Two Seasons Summer Camp, circa 1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Installation Photographs, Painting in the United States (1949), Carnegie Institute, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
    (Includes installation views and related material)
  - Photographs of Artwork by G. Tooker, circa 1960s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Transparencies and Slides of Artwork by G. Tooker, circa 1960-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Contact Sheets and Negatives of Artwork by G. Tooker, W. Christopher, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Photographs and Contact Sheets of William Christopher Artwork, circa 1960s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Slides of Artwork by William Christopher, circa 1960s-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Negatives and Transparencies of William Christopher Artwork, circa 1950-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Photographs of Furniture, Cabinets by William Christopher, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Photographs of Student Artwork, W. Christopher Student at Dartmouth College, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, circa 1959-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous Artwork Photographs, circa 1960s-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)